A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Public Safety, 1990; 1992; 1996; 1998-2010 (bulk 2002-2009)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Secretary of Public Safety, 1990; 1992; 1996; 1998-2010 (bulk 2002-2009)
The Library of Virginia
44680, 44702
34.75 cubic feet (38 boxes)
Virginia. Office of the Secretary of Public Safety
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78. Privacy-protected information has been flagged and/or sealed, but not removed from the collection. Restricted information may include, but is not limited to: attorney-client privileged documents, medical information, social security numbers, and Department of Corrections inmate classification material.
Acquisition Information
Accession 44680 transferred by Martha Hazelgrove, Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, 1111 E. Broad Street, Richmond, Virginia, 12 January 2010.
Accession 44702 transferred by the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, 14 January 2010.
Historical Information
n 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties. Compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governor's top management team.
The office of the Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety was created on April 8, 1972. Originally, the Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety oversaw the State Highway Commission, Division of Motor Vehicles, Department of State Police, Highway Safety Division, Office of Emergency Services, Department of Military Affairs, Virginia State Crime Commission, and the Law Enforcement Officers Training Standards Commission. Since that time, the Office has undergone a series of administrative reorganizations. On April 12, 1976, the Legislature established separate secretariats for transportation and public safety, effective July 1, 1976. On July 1, 1984, the offices were again combined. Finally, the two became separate offices on February 22, 1990, and have remained separate in the years since.
The Secretary of Public Safety is a member of the Governor's Cabinet, is appointed by the governor, and is subject to confirmation by the General Assembly. Throughout Governor Mark R. Warner's term (2002-2006), the Secretary of Public Safety was responsible for the direction of, or had jurisdiction over, 11 state agencies and boards. The agencies and boards under the heading of the Secretary of Public Safety during the Warner administration are as follows: Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, Department of Correctional Education, Department of Corrections, Department of Criminal Justice Services, Department of Emergency Management, Department of Fire Programs, Department of Juvenile Justice, Department of Military Affairs, the Virginia Parole Board, and the Virginia State Police. The Department of Veterans Services was added to the Public Safety Secretariat during Governor Timothy R. Kaine's administration (2006-2010).
On December 20, 2001, Governor-elect Mark R. Warner appointed John W. Marshall as his Secretary of Public Safety. Prior to taking this position, Marshall had served as a trooper, special agent, training academy instructor, and sergeant with the Virginia State Police. In 1994, President William J. Clinton appointed Marshall to serve as the United States Marshal for the Eastern District of Virginia. In 1999, he was nominated to serve as director of the United States Marshals Service. He was the first African-American to hold this position. On December 9, 2005, Governor-elect Tim Kaine re-appointed Marshall as Secretary of Public Safety. He served until the end of the Kaine administration in January 2010.
Scope and Content
The Secretary of Public Safety records consists of thirty-eight archival boxes and are divided into six series. Series have been designated for Correspondence-Assigned State Agencies, Correspondence and Supporting Documentation-Office of the Secretary, Decision Memoranda and Briefs, Federal Grant Funding, Legislative Files, and Special Projects and Studies. These records document the activities of the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, as well as the agencies and boards which fall under its heading, during the gubernatorial terms of Governor Mark R. Warner (2002-2006) and Governor Timothy M. Kaine (2006-2010).
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Assigned State Agencies, 1996; 1999-2010
Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, 1990; 1992; 1998-2009
Subseries A. Correspondence Files, 2002-2009
Subseries B. Subject Files, 1990; 1992; 2001-2009
Subseries C. Records of Deputy Secretary Barry Green, 1998-2005
Subseries D. Records of Assistant Secretary Dawn Smith, 2002-2008
Subseries E. Records of Assistant Secretary/Deputy Secretary Marilyn Harris, 2002-2007
Series III. Decision Memoranda and Briefs, 2005-2010
Series IV. Federal Grant Funding, 2002-2009
Series V. Legislative Files, 2002-2003; 2005-2009
Series VI. Special Projects and Studies, 2002; 2004-2009.
Related Material
The Library of Virginia Email Project - Governor Tim Kaine Portal includes over 6,000 emails from 11 Warner and Kaine administration Public Safety staff members: John Marshall, Clyde Cristman, Marilyn Harris, Dawn Smith, Erin Bryant, Susan Gholson, Jacklyn Varela, Iva Frizzle, Martha Hazelgrove, Gabrielle Williams, and Beth Camphouse.
The Governor Tim Kaine Administration Web Archive Collection, 2006-2010 includes the archived website of the Secretary of Public Safety. The archived website contains information on public safety initiatives, office information, and agency information.
The Governor Mark R. Warner Administration Web Archive Collection, 2002-2006 includes the archived website of the Secretary of Public Safety. The archived website contains information on public safety initiatives, office information, and agency information.
The Timothy M. Kaine Administration (2006-2010) Cabinet Weekly Reports digital collection includes the Secretary of Public Safety's weekly reports to Governor Kaine.
Other collections related to the Secretary of Public Safety include:
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Executive Office-Governor, Records, 2005-2009.
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Executive Office-Chief of Staff, Records, 2006-2009.
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Executive Office-Counselor's Office, Records, 2001-2009 (bulk 2006-2009)
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Policy Office, Records, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009).
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Press Office, Records, 2004-2010 (bulk 2006-2009).
A Guide to the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Public Safety Records, 2000-2006 (bulk 2002-2005).
A Guide to the Governor Mark R. Warner, Executive Office Records, 2001-2006.
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Assigned State Agencies, 1996; 1999-2010., Extent: 11.0 cu. ft. (11 boxes) (Box 1-11)
  The Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Assigned State Agencies series is housed in 11 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by agency. Restricted material related to terrorism, personnel records, and administrative investigations has been sealed but not removed. This series contains correspondence, along with supporting material such as agendas, reports, policies, and presentations. The following state agencies and boards operated under the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety during the Kaine administration: Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, the Department of Correctional Education, Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, the Department of Corrections, the Department of Criminal Justice Services, the Department of Emergency Management, the Department of Fire Programs, the Department of Forensic Science, the Department of Juvenile Justice, the Department of Military Affairs, the Virginia Parole Board, the Virginia State Police, and the Department of Veterans Services.
  The correspondence files contain mostly correspondence between the agencies and the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety regarding issues that affect that particular agency or board. References to budgetary matters, litigation, studies and reports, board appointments, and legislation are frequently found in this material. These files also provide supporting documentation and background information on many topics.
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Department of
    - Audit Reports, 2006-2009. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Brochures, Posters and Advertisements, 2006; undated. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 2007-2009. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 2006-2009. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Governor Kaine's visit to ABC, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - National Alcoholic Beverage Control Association Conference, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Plan to Merge ABC's Bureau of Law Enforcement with Department of State Police (Drafts), 15 September 2003. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Plan to Merge ABC's Bureau of Law Enforcement with Department of State Police (Final), 15 October 2003. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Senate Finance Presentation, Public Safety Subcommittee, 13 February 2004. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Reports, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Reports, 2008. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Three-Tier System (DPB/ABC), 2004. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correctional Education, Department of
    - Functional Literacy Program Report, June 2006. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Audit Report, 2008. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 2005-2009. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Reports, 2003; 2005-2007. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Strategic Plan, 2005-2010. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Vocational Programs, Report of, October 2006. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council
    - Audit Reports, 2004-2008. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - General Correspondence, 2004-2007. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Corrections, Department of
    - Alexandria P and P District Lease, 2008. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Alternatives for Non-Violent Offenders Task Force, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Audit Reports (Parole Board and Correctional Education), 2008. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Budget Records, 2003. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Budget Records, 2005-2007. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Budget Records, 2008. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Budget Records, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Charlotte County Prison, 2007-2008. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Communicable Diseases, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Community Release Program Notifications, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Community Release Program Notifications, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Community Release Program Notifications, 2008. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Community Release Program Notifications, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Commutations, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Construction Reports, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Corrections, Board of, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Culpeper Jail, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Demographics Report (Quarterly), 2002. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Director Position Interviews, 2002. (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Emery, Bill (God's X Gangsters), 2004. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - EPA Violations (Greensville Correctional Center), 2002-2003. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - EPA Violations (Greensville Correctional Center), 2003-2004. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Executions, 2006-2009. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Federal Prisoners, Status of, 2002. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Food Service Privatization, 2002-2004. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Forecast Policy Advisory Committee, 2009. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Gemeinshaft, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Ghost Fleet, 2003. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Governor's Corrections Facility Task Force, Meeting Materials, 2002. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Governor's Corrections Facility Task Force Final Report, 2002. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Grooming Policy, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Highland Beef Farms - Jay Hersch, 2008. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Inmate Demographics, 2002-2003. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Inmate Forecast Policy Advisory Committee, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Inmate Release Debit Card, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Inmate Work Crew - Capitol Square, 2002-2003. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Jail Overcrowding, 2002-2003. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - JLARC Budget Review, 2008. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Labor Force Projections, 2008. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Lawrenceville Correctional Center Security Operations Review, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Laws and Regulations, 2002. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Lawson Review Case, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Lawsuits, 2002-2003. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Marshall, Antoine, 2008. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Governor's Corrections Facility Task Force Final Report, 2002. (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Master Plan, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - McShin Foundation, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Media Policy, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Medical Costs, 2007-2008. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Meherrin River Regional Jail, 2009. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Mt. Rogers PPEA (Grayson County), 2006-2007 (1 of 2). (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Mt. Rogers PPEA (Grayson County), 2006-2007 (2 of 2). (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - New Facilities - Naming, 2006-2007. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Non-Violent Risk Assessment, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Offender Population Forecasting, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Offender Population Forecasts, 2005. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Offender Population Forecasting Policy Advisory Committee, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Offender Population Forecasting Policy Advisory Committee, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Offender Population Forecasting Policy Advisory Committee, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Offender Population Forecasting Policy Advisory Committee, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Offender Population Forecasting Policy Advisory Committee, 2008. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Offender Population Forecasting Policy Advisory Committee, 2009. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Offender Populations Forecasts, 2001-2004. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Offender Populations, State and Local Expenditures for Housing Offenders, and Related Issues, 12 August 2008. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Offender Reentry Program, 2004. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Offender Transition Program, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Out-of-State Revenues, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Pardon: Crawford-Daniels, Ollin Renaye, 2008. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Parole Revocation, 2008. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Patrick County Jail, 2007-2008 (1 of 2). (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Patrick County Jail, 2007-2008 (2 of 2). (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Plumbing Controls Program (ICON), 2003. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Population Summaries, 2001-2002; 2007. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Pound Day Reporting Center - Del. Bud Phillips, 2008. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Prison Fellowship, 2006-2008. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Prisoner Reentry (DPB), 2007. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Prisoner Reentry Policy Academy, 2006 (1 of 3). (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Prisoner Reentry Policy Academy, 2006 (2 of 3). (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Prisoner Reentry Policy Academy, 2006 (3 of 3). (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Prisoner Reentry Policy Academy, 2006-2008. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Prisoner Reentry Policy Academy, 2008 (1 of 2). (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Prisoner Reentry Policy Academy, 2008 (2 of 2). (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Probation and Parole Issues, 2002. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Probation and Parole Leases, 2006-2007. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Recidivism, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Regional Office Structure Reorganization, 2002. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Reprieves, 2007-2009. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Reports and Studies, 2000-2001. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Reports, 2001-2002. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Reports, 2003-2004; 2007. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Reports, 2007-2008. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Department of Corrections, Management Information Summary Annual Reports, 2007 and 2008. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Security Staff Compensation Plan, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Sexually Violent Predators (SVP) Forecast, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Statewide Community-based Corrections System Strategic Planning Status Report, 2002. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Statewide Community-based Corrections System Status Report (2001-2002), 2003. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Statewide Community-based Corrections System Status Reports 2006-2009. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Report on the Department of Corrections on Plan for the Closure of Staunton Correctional Center, 2002. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Video Visitation - Dr. Cardwell, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Beach Jail Lawsuit, 2008 (1 of 2). (Folder 18)
    - Virginia Beach Jail Lawsuit, 2008 (2 of 2). (Folder 19)
    - Virginia Correctional Center for Women, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Correctional Information System (VACORIS), 2006-2007. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Department of
    - ABC/VSP Merger, 2003. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - ABC/VSP Merger, 2003. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Attorney General, 2009. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Anti-Gang Workgroup, 2008. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Audit Reports, 2006-2008. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Blueprints for Change: Criminal Justice Policy Issues in Virginia, 2006-2007. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Board Appointments, 2009. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Budget, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Crime Rates, 2005. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Criminal Justice Services Board Meeting Records, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Electromagnetic Pulse Attack (EMP) Report, 2004. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Grants, 2002. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Identity Theft, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report of the Virginia Advisory Committee on Juvenile Justice, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Piedmont Court Services Annual Reports, 2007 and 2008. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Presentations and Reports, 2008. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Restructuring, 2008-2009. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Richmond Continuum Evaluation, February 2002. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Statewide Criminal Justice Plan, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Training and Delivery Methods for Criminal Justice Officers, 2004. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Management, Department of
    - 2008 Hurricane Evacuation Study, 2008. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 2008 Hurricane Brief Background Data, 18 August 2008. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 2009 Hurricane Season Overview, 2009. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Audit Report, 2006-2008. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Emergency/Disaster Responsibilities of the Governor of Virginia, Presented to Chief of Staff Wayne Turnage, 4 June 2007. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Dept. of Social Services, Family Assistance Plan (draft), 17 December 2007. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency, Space Object Re-entry Concept of Operations Plan, undated. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Grants Management System, 2006. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Joint Training Proposal - Korean National Emergency Management Agency, 2007. (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - National Emergency Management Association, 2005 Hurricane Season Response, After-Action Report, October 2006. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - VERTEX 2005 After-Action Report, 2005. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Virginia 2009 Senior Leadership Tabletop Exercise - After-Action Report, 2009 (RESTRICTED). (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Emergency Operations Center (VEOC), 2006. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Emergency Services and Disaster Laws, 2001; 2006. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Fire Programs, Department of
    - Audit Report, 2006-2008. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Arson Briefing and Recommendations, February 2004. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Board Appointments, 2009. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Report: Capabilities and Long-Term Need for an Effective Maritime Fire Fighting Team in the Hampton Roads Region, Recommendations for Organization and Funding Priorities, 1999. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Fire Marshal Transfer, 2006-2007. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Fire Programs Fund, 2007. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 2002-2005. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Reports, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Report: Fighting Fires with Facts, April 2007. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Strategic Plan Review, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Department of Fire Programs Talking Points, 5 September 2008. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Transition Information and Materials, 2002. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Fallen Firefighter Memorial Service, 2005. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Fire Chiefs' Association, Statewide Emergency Response Annex, Draft Version 8, 13 January 2008. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Fire Fighters Academy, 2006-2008. (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Fire Services Board Meeting, 3-4 June 2005. (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Fire Services Board Meeting, 24-25 February 2006. (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Virginia Fire Services Board Meeting, 2-3 June 2006. (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Fire Services Board Meeting, 31 May-2 June 2007. (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Fire Services Board Meeting, 16-18 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Virginia Fire Services Board Meeting, 18-19 December 2007. (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Fire and Life Safety Coalition, 2009. (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Virginia Fire Prevention and Control Plan, 18 April 2008. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Forensic Science, Department of
    - Audit Report, 2006-2008. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Compensation Plan, 2005. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Data Security Review, 2006. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Director Position, 2006 (RESTRICTED). (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - DNA Databank/Missing Samples, 2006-2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - DNA Testing/Mary Jane Burton Cases, 2007-2008. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 7, Folder 13)